<BlogsEntry>
  <__cachedModel>false</__cachedModel>
  <__new>false</__new>
  <__uuid>32ae6a6e-9e61-42a0-9839-9847be23c351</__uuid>
  <__originalUuid>32ae6a6e-9e61-42a0-9839-9847be23c351</__originalUuid>
  <__entryId>46922</__entryId>
  <__groupId>10184</__groupId>
  <__originalGroupId>10184</__originalGroupId>
  <__setOriginalGroupId>false</__setOriginalGroupId>
  <__companyId>10157</__companyId>
  <__originalCompanyId>10157</__originalCompanyId>
  <__setOriginalCompanyId>false</__setOriginalCompanyId>
  <__userId>11233</__userId>
  <__userUuid>aa08a748-7b1c-43e3-99a6-c116c80fdb1d</__userUuid>
  <__originalUserId>11233</__originalUserId>
  <__setOriginalUserId>false</__setOriginalUserId>
  <__userName>Test Test</__userName>
  <__createDate class="sql-timestamp">2014-07-11 19:24:50.338</__createDate>
  <__modifiedDate class="sql-timestamp">2014-07-11 19:33:33.086</__modifiedDate>
  <__title>Hipster Blog Example</__title>
  <__urlTitle>hipster-blog-example</__urlTitle>
  <__originalUrlTitle>hipster-blog-example</__originalUrlTitle>
  <__description></__description>
  <__content>&lt;p id=&quot;yui_patched_v3_11_0_1_1405106904270_918&quot;&gt;&lt;span id=&quot;yui_patched_v3_11_0_1_1405106904270_917&quot; style=&quot;font-size:16px;&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; id=&quot;yui_patched_v3_11_0_1_1405106904270_916&quot; src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/qMvu3tw.png&quot; style=&quot;width: 450px; height: 354px; margin: 10px; float: left;&quot; /&gt;Meggings tote bag disrupt fashion axe, Thundercats forage Marfa Banksy vinyl. Paleo seitan mustache, keffiyeh art party tattooed stumptown craft beer shabby chic organic 90&apos;s gluten-free. Fashion axe salvia letterpress, +1 butcher before they sold out XOXO. Selfies bitters Austin ennui, Wes Anderson Truffaut food truck narwhal seitan McSweeney&apos;s. Tattooed chambray pop-up iPhone. Mlkshk polaroid Shoreditch, freegan Williamsburg keffiyeh hella narwhal Carles cray yr Echo Park meggings typewriter food truck. Asymmetrical selvage Etsy, bespoke Thundercats put a bird on it Intelligentsia Banksy hashtag.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:16px;&quot;&gt;3 wolf moon yr iPhone meggings cardigan, mustache semiotics mixtape dreamcatcher Truffaut viral Bushwick actually. Wolf Portland ugh quinoa, selvage put a bird on it craft beer small batch distillery. Sartorial pug aesthetic YOLO, locavore vegan Odd Future yr literally gastropub Wes Anderson stumptown. Ethical chia High Life, before they sold out umami Portland crucifix try-hard food truck American Apparel Truffaut lomo Bushwick Carles. Plaid disrupt Odd Future Pinterest Austin, art party authentic DIY lo-fi meggings Tonx High Life twee. Organic beard church-key, letterpress artisan drinking vinegar small batch normcore flexitarian you probably haven&apos;t heard of them squid before they sold out vegan. Wes Anderson chia readymade, Echo Park whatever kale chips fingerstache trust fund Thundercats paleo Blue Bottle four loko PBR&amp;B synth cornhole.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:16px;&quot;&gt;Banksy artisan aesthetic beard sartorial squid, VHS hoodie fixie shabby chic pug Wes Anderson before they sold out yr. Semiotics Schlitz Pitchfork beard Vice, hashtag literally cardigan retro sartorial pickled Shoreditch. Ethical Tumblr Cosby sweater, crucifix jean shorts pickled wolf dreamcatcher put a bird on it banjo Carles. Bespoke farm-to-table Bushwick next level Pitchfork sustainable ethnic, tattooed authentic 3 wolf moon bitters hella. Thundercats beard art party food truck pork belly kogi. Whatever pork belly cornhole, pour-over 8-bit art party stumptown bespoke paleo four loko narwhal letterpress photo booth. Schlitz whatever vinyl Pinterest chillwave, Banksy Cosby sweater Austin put a bird on it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:16px;&quot;&gt;90&apos;s selvage Intelligentsia DIY letterpress shabby chic. Ennui occupy bicycle rights Williamsburg, DIY dreamcatcher Schlitz. Hoodie normcore crucifix Pitchfork Odd Future, DIY keffiyeh swag Schlitz Carles hashtag. Street art asymmetrical wolf, XOXO Vice seitan bitters scenester American Apparel. Occupy hoodie organic leggings. Plaid farm-to-table food truck, salvia stumptown Kickstarter pug. Cray try-hard actually, DIY church-key normcore semiotics kale chips forage pork belly Schlitz next level direct trade vegan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</__content>
  <__displayDate class="sql-timestamp">2014-07-11 19:24:00.0</__displayDate>
  <__originalDisplayDate class="sql-timestamp" reference="../__displayDate"/>
  <__allowPingbacks>false</__allowPingbacks>
  <__allowTrackbacks>true</__allowTrackbacks>
  <__trackbacks></__trackbacks>
  <__smallImage>true</__smallImage>
  <__smallImageId>46923</__smallImageId>
  <__smallImageURL>http://i.imgur.com/qMvu3tw.png </__smallImageURL>
  <__status>0</__status>
  <__originalStatus>0</__originalStatus>
  <__setOriginalStatus>false</__setOriginalStatus>
  <__statusByUserId>11233</__statusByUserId>
  <__statusByUserName>Test Test</__statusByUserName>
  <__statusDate class="sql-timestamp">2014-07-11 19:33:33.086</__statusDate>
  <__columnBitmask>0</__columnBitmask>
</BlogsEntry>